<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Google_Analytics_Assignment</string>
    <string name="l1">
            Laptop name : Mi Notebook Pro 14
            Operating system : Windows 10
            RAM : 16GB
            weight : 1.5Kg
            description : Mi Notebook Pro 14 is a Windows 10 laptop with a 14.00-inch display that has a resolution of 2560x1600 pixels. It is powered by a Core i5 processor and it comes with 16GB of RAM. The Mi Notebook Pro 14 packs 512GB of SSD storage.
    </string>
    <string name="l2">
            Laptop name : Lenovo 500w Gen 3
            Operating system : Windows 8
            RAM : 8GB
            weight : 2.7Kg
            description :  Lenovo 14w Gen 2 specifications, features Lenovo 14w Gen 2 comes with up to Windows 10 Pro. It features a 14-inch display that comes in HD resolution and full-HD resolution with options for different brightness levels and touch input. The laptop is powered by the dual-core AMD 3015e Processor with integrated graphics.
    </string>
    <string name="l3">
            Laptop name : Apple MacBook Air MRE82HN/A
            Operating system : Windows 10
            RAM : 12GB
            weight : 1.25Kg
            description : Apple MacBook Air MRE82HN/A is a macOS laptop with a 13.30-inch display that has a resolution of 2560x1600 pixels. It is powered by a Core i5 processor and it comes with 8GB of RAM. The Apple MacBook Air MRE82HN/A packs 128GB of SSD storage.
    </string>
    <string name="l4">
            laptop name : HP ProBook
            Operating system : Windows 7
            RAM : 16GB
            weight : 2.0Kg
            description : Windows 7 Pro or other operating systems Intel® Core™ i3, i5, and i7 processors (dual and quad core) 14.0" diagonal HD (1366 x 768), HD+ (1600 x 900) or FHD (1920 x 1080) display Take on tasks in the office or on the road.
    </string>
    <string name="l5">
            Laptop name : HP NoteBook 445 G8
            Operating system : Windows 10
            RAM : 4GB
            weight : 2.4Kg
            description : Windows 10 Pro or other operating systems Intel® Core™ i3, i5, and i7 processors (dual core) 15.6" diagonal HD (1366 x 768) display, FHD (1920 x 1080), or HD Touchscreen (1366 x 768) display Delivers powerful performance in the office or on the go.
    </string>

    <string name="m1">
            Mobile name : Apple iPhone XS Max
            launch : 2018
            RAM : 4GB
            Storage : 64 GB
            Price : $ 430.83 / £ 309.95
    </string>
    <string name="m2">
            Mobile name : Apple iPhone 6 Plu
            launch : 2014
            RAM : 1GB
            Storage : 16 GB
            Price : $ 230.83 / £ 250
    </string>
    <string name="m3">
            Mobile name : Huawei Y7a
            launch : 2018
            RAM : 4GB
            Storage : 32 GB
            Price : $ 150 / £ 200
    </string>
    <string name="m4">
            Mobile name : Samsung Galaxy A52
            launch : 2019
            RAM : 6GB
            Storage : 64 GB
            Price : $ 300 / £ 309
    </string>
    <string name="m5">
            Mobile name : Samsung Galaxy S20
            launch : 2020
            RAM : 8GB
            Storage : 64 GB
            Price : $ 700 / £ 720
    </string>


    <string name="f1">
            Mail name : Kabaab
            description : Kebabs are various cooked meat dishes with their origins in Middle Eastern cuisine. Numerous variants are popular around the world.
            Price :	$ 7
    </string>
    <string name="f2">
            Mail name : Pizza
            description : is a savory dish of Italian origin consisting of a usually round, flattened base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomatoes, cheese, and often various other ingredients (such as anchovies, mushrooms, onions, olives, pineapple, meat, etc.), which is then baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven.[1] A small pizza is sometimes called a pizzetta. A person who makes pizza is known as a pizzaiolo.
            Price :	$ 12
    </string>
    <string name="f3">
            Mail name : Shawarma
            description : consisting of meat cut into thin slices, stacked in a cone-like shape, and roasted on a slowly-turning vertical rotisserie or spit. Originally made of lamb or mutton, todays shawarma may also be chicken, turkey, beef, or veal.[5][6][1] Thin slices are shaved off the cooked surface as it. continuously rotates.
            Price :	$ 5
    </string>
    <string name="f4">
            Mail name : Grilled chiken
            description : Sometimes in cooking the simplest dishes are the hardest to get right, and grilled chicken is a perfect example. Because boneless chicken breasts are so lean, they often turn out dry, rubbery, and bland.
            Price :	$ 10
    </string>
    <string name="f5">
           Mail name : Drinks
            description :is a liquid intended for human consumption. In addition to their basic function of satisfying thirst, drinks play important roles in human culture. Common types of drinks include plain drinking water, milk, coffee, tea, hot chocolate, juice and soft drinks.
            Price :	$ 1
    </string>


    <string name="c1">
            Clothes name : Cap
            description :A cap is a kind of soft and flat headgear, usually with a visor. Caps have crowns that fit very close to the head. They made their first appearance as early as 3,200BC.[1] Caps typically have a visor, or no brim at all
            Price :	$ 3
    </string>
    <string name="c2">
            Clothes name : Shirt
            description :A shirt is a cloth garment for the upper body (from the neck to the waist).Originally an undergarment worn exclusively by men, it has become, in American English, a catch-all term for a broad variety of upper-body garments and undergarments.
            Price :	$ 5
    </string>
    <string name="c3">
            Clothes name : Jacket
            description :A jacket is a garment for the upper body, usually extending below the hips.[1] A jacket typically has sleeves, and fastens in the front or slightly on the side. A jacket is generally lighter, tighter-fitting, and less insulating than a coat, which is outerwear.
        Price :	$ 20
    </string>
    <string name="c4">
            Clothes name : Jeans
            description :Jeans are a type of pants or trousers, typically made from denim or dungaree cloth. Often the term "jeans" refers to a particular style of trousers, called "blue jeans", which were invented by Jacob W. Davis in partnership with Levi Strauss
        Price :	$ 15
    </string>
    <string name="c5">
            Clothes name : Shoes
            description : A shoe is an item of footwear intended to protect and comfort the human foot. Shoes are also used as an item of decoration and fashion.
        Price :	$ 12
    </string>

    <string name="e1">
            Device name : Refrigerator
            modal : 2018
            description : is a home appliance consisting of a thermally insulated compartment and a heat pump (mechanical, electronic or chemical) that transfers heat from its inside to its external environment so that its inside is cooled to a temperature below the room temperature.
             Price :	$ 500
    </string>
    <string name="e2">
            Device name : Washer
            modal : 2016
            description : is a thin plate (typically disk-shaped, but sometimes square) with a hole (typically in the middle) that is normally used to distribute the load of a threaded fastener, such as a bolt or nut. Other uses are as a spacer, spring (Belleville washer
            Price :	$ 200
    </string>
    <string name="e3">
            Device name : Conditioner
            modal : 2014
            description : is the process of removing heat and controlling the humidity as well as removing dust in some cases of the air within a building or vehicle to achieve a more comfortable interior environment.
            Price :	$ 350
    </string>
    <string name="e4">
            Device name : Fan
            modal : 2020
            description : is a powered machine used to create a flow of air. A fan consists of a rotating arrangement of vanes or blades, which act on the air. The rotating assembly of blades and hub is known as an impeller, rotor, or runner
            Price :	$ 50
    </string>
    <string name="e5">
            Device name : Microwave
            modal : 2019
            description : is an electric oven that heats and cooks food by exposing it to electromagnetic radiation in the microwave frequency range.
             Price : $ 100
    </string>

</resources>